Kettel and Idols
Now then, let's get to the main project.
Please give me a cute title call
My three main elements
Now, this is the section where we ask you to introduce the three elements that make up yourself.
Yes, I am.
Now, please tell us your three elements, Yasumoto-san.
Yes, I do. Here are my three major elements.
Doran!
1. beauty
2. music
3. reading.
I think beauty goes along with what you just said about toothpaste.
I love to improve myself.
I also like to take a sauna and take care of my skin.
I like to take a sauna and take care of my skin.
I like to think about what kind of lotion I should use and what kind of things are good for my skin.
I like to look up trivia about what's good for my skin.
I'm a beauty geek.
You have "beauty" in your profile on your Instagram, don't you?
Yes, I'm a beauty skin specialist.
I took this picture when I was about the age of the Corona Disaster.
So, that's why I'm a beauty geek.
Do you have to study and take an exam?
Yes, they send me some kind of textbook.
You study it and take an exam later.
After that, you take an exam and get an award.
Well, I was wondering if there were any members of the Municipal Junior High School of Art and Design who were interested in joining the program.
They would ask me to teach them something.
Do they ask you to teach them something good for their skin?
Well, Nonoka, my sister, Nonoka, asked me.
Maybe, but Nonoka is very serious.
Maybe because Aya likes beauty.
Like, if I talk about beauty, she'll talk about it.
Inside, I think she listens to me a little too forcefully and forcibly.
I think she listens to me as a chance to talk.
Maybe she's listening to me as a chance to talk.
I can feel her kindness.
But I'm getting a pimple here.
What do you think I should do? She asks me, "What do you think I should do?
I'll ask her what I should do, and she'll recommend a product to use at the right time.
or give advice on food, etc.
You know...
I do that sometimes.
Oh, I see.
By the way, do you have any recommendations for the Yakami-kun generation?
Well, I guess, as they say, continuity is the key to success.
And the most important thing is to wash your face.
Cleansing and washing face are very important.
Men also produce sebum more easily than women.
They also have large pores.
Even if they are not wearing makeup, it is very important to wash their face.
Clogged pores are caused by sebum.
I really want men to know the importance of washing and cleansing their face.
That alone can really lead to beautiful skin.
I see.
By the way, Yagami, you bought a Rifa shower head about a year ago.
Isn't it a good one? It's a good one.
I use the mist mode to cleanse my face, and it's helped reduce my pimples a lot.
It's important to use a fine mist.
What is the temperature of the hot water?
Rifa is really great, isn't it? It's better for the skin if it's warm.
I see.
Then that's wonderful. It'll make you beautiful.
But now that you recommend it...
Your skin is so smooth and shiny, you're very persuasive.
I almost raised my hand and said I'd buy it.
Really? It's as smooth as a glistening arrowhead.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
I know it sounds like I'm trying to sound cool, but...
Making music...
This show...
Mr. Careless
Kogesaka
Kazuma-san
Takimaru Taki-chan
Megi-san provided this program.
Thank you very much!